{
    "subject": "resource/Sinclair_Vehicles",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Historic_electric_vehicles",
    "human_readable": "The topic of Sinclair Vehicles is Historic Electric Vehicles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8549273610115051,
            "question": "Are there any specific models of historic electric vehicles that Sinclair Vehicles focuses on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378569483757019,
            "question": "What makes a vehicle considered 'historic' by Sinclair Vehicles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7886605858802795,
            "question": "Does Sinclair Vehicles offer restoration services for historic electric vehicles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6969820857048035,
            "question": "How does Sinclair Vehicles contribute to the understanding of early automotive history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6666410565376282,
            "question": "What is the significance of preserving historic electric vehicles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5488066673278809,
            "question": "How has the interest in historic electric vehicles evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.501876175403595,
            "question": "What era do the vehicles offered by Sinclair Vehicles come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48055100440979004,
            "question": "What type of vehicles does Sinclair Vehicles specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45349523425102234,
            "question": "Are there any modern technologies incorporated into Sinclair Vehicles' offerings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2707710266113281,
            "question": "What is the target audience for Sinclair Vehicles' products and services?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The topic of Sinclair Vehicles is Historic Electric Vehicles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5332_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any modern technologies incorporated into Sinclair Vehicles' offerings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5332_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of vehicles does Sinclair Vehicles specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5332_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era do the vehicles offered by Sinclair Vehicles come from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5332_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5332_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents discuss the history and details of the Sinclair C5, which is an example of a historic electric vehicle. Therefore, the statement that \"the topic of Sinclair Vehicles is Historic Electric Vehicles\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The topic of Sinclair Vehicles is primarily about Electric Vehicles, but not only Historic Electric Vehicles since the company was active and producing electric vehicles as late as the 1980s, which makes them more recent than historic.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text details the Sinclair C5 as a product of its time, facing commercial failure due to technological limitations and market readiness.  It also mentions Sir Clive Sinclair's continued interest in electric vehicles, hinting at ongoing development beyond just the C5.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information describes the Sinclair C5 as a \"small one-person battery electric recumbent tricycle\" which does not necessarily imply that it is historic, and also mentions other projects from the company like the C1, which suggests that they are still active in the electric vehicle market.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information primarily focuses on the Sinclair C5, a specific historic electric vehicle project by Sir Clive Sinclair. While the topic does involve an historic electric vehicle, it also discusses ongoing efforts and plans for future electric vehicles by Sinclair Vehicles Ltd, indicating that the company was not solely dedicated to past projects but had aspirations for modern developments as well.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}